http://www.itvplc.com/site-services/privacy

About ITV
What we doOur strategyMarket reviewBoard of DirectorsManagement teamHistory
Investors
Investor propositionResults centreRegulatory newsOther corporate newsFinancial calendarShare priceShareholder informationGovernance
Social purpose
HomeOur purposeBetter healthInclusionEnvironmentGiving backNewsDownloads
ITV HubPress centreCareersContact us
About ITV
What we doOur strategyMarket reviewBoard of DirectorsManagement teamHistory
201720162015201420132012201120102006200520041998199419731955
Governance
PoliciesSubsidiary s.172 StatementsTerms of referenceDirectors
Privacy
This Notice explains how ITV Plc (“ITV”, “us” or “we”) collect and use personal data obtained from users of our website. ITV is the data controller in respect of the personal data we collect and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This Notice should be read together with our Cookies Statement.
What personal data we collect
We may collect personal data from those who visit our website. Some areas of the website offer you newsletters, marketing communications, publications and information about our company, or to contact us with enquiries and comments. We may collect and process personal data about you such as:
your name, address, email address and other details such as your occupation and country of residence;
where you subscribe, you email alert preferences; and
records of your correspondence with us, if you have contacted us.
When you use the website, we collect certain technical information that is sent by your browser to our website (stored as log files). This includes information, such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, language, time zone setting, access times and any referring website addresses.
How we use personal data we collect and the legal bases we rely on
Depending on the situation, we may use personal data collected from you through the site in the following ways:
to ensure that the website is presented to you in an effective manner;
to provide you with information that you have requested from us; and
where you have registered to do so, to send you electronic marketing, ITV company updates and other materials relating to our services.
Where you chose to sign up to our email alerts (for example, AGM updates, acquisition and alliances, financial results, ITV news, portfolio news alerts etc.), we process your personal data on the basis that you have consented to receive these updates.
You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ button in any of our emails, or by visiting our email alerts page here and changing your preferences. If you unsubscribe from all communications, we may still retain your email address so we know not to contact you.
Sometimes, we process your personal data because it is in our legitimate interests to maintain and promote our services and properly administer our business, for example, when you contact us and submit a query.
Sharing your personal data
We may share your personal data with third parties, including:
government and regulatory authorities, for example to respond to a legal request or comply with a legal obligation;
suppliers of IT services (such as those needed to operate this website) and third parties engaged by ITV for the purpose of providing marketing communications or services requested by you; and
in the event that we sell, buy or merge any business or assets, including to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets and their respective professional advisers.
Storage and transfers
Your personal data is kept for as long as it is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. Therefore, after this period data is destroyed, erased or anonymised. In order to provide our services and the website, any personal data that we obtain may be transferred to and stored by a third party at a locality inside or outside the UK or the European Economic Area (EEA), including in a country where the law provides less protection for personal data. If we transfer personal data to a third party outside of the UK or EEA, we will, as required by applicable law, ensure that your privacy rights are protected by appropriate safeguards to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. In particular, appropriate data protection may be provided by an agreement entered into by us containing the model clauses which permit such transfer. You can find a link to the model clauses at https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries en. Please contact us if you would like more information about the safeguards we use to protect your personal data when we transfer it outside of the UK or EEA.
Your rights
Applicable data privacy laws may give rights to individuals in respect of personal data that organisations hold about them, for example to:
request a copy of the personal data that we hold about them;
object to the processing of their personal data;
request that we rectify, delete, or limit the processing of their personal data; and
not be subject to a decision based solely on automated means, where these decisions have a legal or similarly significant impact on them.
To make any requests regarding your personal data, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding your personal data, please submit your written request to us at privacy@itv.com. You may also have the right to object to your personal data being used for certain purposes, including to send you marketing. We will comply with any requests to exercise your rights in accordance with applicable law. Please be aware, however, that there are a number of limitations to these rights, and there may be circumstances where we are not able to comply with your request. You are also entitled to raise your concerns with your local supervisory authority for data protection.
Contact us
If you have a concern or complaint about how ITV has used your personal data, as a first step, you should raise this with ITV, via the email address privacy@itv.com or by writing to us at:
ITV PLC
2 Waterhouse Square
140 Holborn
London
EC1N 2AE
United Kingdom
Changes to this Notice
We reserve the right to modify or amend this Notice at any time and will always post the revised Notice on our website.
